Woke up in a tab I forgot to save
Screenshare of a life I don't wanna play
Profile pic smiles but the eyes gone gray
너도 알잖아
I scroll past texts that I never sent
Typed your name out
Hit backspace again
Every blue light halo feels like blame
Breathing in static
Calling it faith
404 heart not found
You log in
I shut down
Every time you come around
(signal lost, signal lost)
Type your love
It errors out
Can you hear me screaming loud?
Or am I just pixel clouds
흐려진 나
흐려진 나 (oh)
Ashtray on the desk
Year-old dust
Plans in a folder I never trust
You said "healing" like it ain't that tough
I said "maybe"
Meaning "I'm stuck"
Lagging on a call I don't wanna end
Watching your mouth move
Can't pretend
Every "it's fine" from you cuts again
반쯤 취해서
I hit send
404 heart not found
You log in
I shut down
Every time you come around
(signal lost, signal lost)
Type your love
It errors out
Can you hear me screaming loud?
Or am I just pixel clouds
흐려진 나
흐려진 나 (yeah)
If I crash here
Would you restart?
Or leave me there
Split apart
Half in Korean
Half in the dark
Half of a joke that went too far
말해 줘
Do you still care?
Or am I ghosts in your DM air?
I'm just a bug you forgot to repair
Just a bug you forgot to repair (mm)
404 heart not found
You log in
I shut down
Every time you come around
(signal lost, signal lost)
Type your love
It errors out
Can you hear me screaming loud?
Or am I just pixel clouds
사라져 나
사라져 나 (fade out)