Left your text on
Read receipts flicker
Screen burn
Coffee gone cold
Eyes sink quicker
Tabs all open
Heart on airplane
Scrolling our old jokes
Like they still explain
I keep buffering on your name
Half-asleep
Half-awake
In the same old frame
Yeah
It hits
But it’s gentle
A sideways ache
All this love in the draft that I never sent
I keep humming you under my breath
Little ghost in the glow of a midnight desk
If we fade
Let it blur
Let it soft-reset
Bittersweet in the lag of a slow disconnect
Your hoodie on
Chair back
Threadbare
Smells like last spring rain
And your chipped black hair
Said “it’s fine”
You were half turned
Now it loops every night
Like a lesson unlearned
I keep buffering on your name
Half-asleep
Half-awake
In the same old frame
Yeah
It hits
But it’s gentle
A sideways ache
All this love in the draft that I never sent
I keep humming you under my breath
Little ghost in the glow of a midnight desk
If we fade
Let it blur
Let it soft-reset
Bittersweet in the lag of a slow disconnect
Mmm
Words slur
Lips stick
Trying not to miss you this much (this much)
If you call
If you don’t
I’ll pretend that I don’t flinch
Don’t rush
I keep buffering on your name
Half-asleep
Half-awake
In the same old frame
Yeah
It hurts
But it’s gentle
A sideways ache
All this love in the draft that I never sent
I keep humming you under my breath
Little ghost in the glow of a midnight desk
If we fade
Let it blur
Let it soft-reset
Bittersweet in the lag of a slow disconnect
I keep buffering on your name
Half-asleep
Half-awake
In the same old frame
Yeah
It hits
But it’s gentle
A sideways ache
All this love in the draft that I never sent